{
    "id": "3390778111c8402eb66df03e4ec3e002",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We walked ……………………… the edge of the desert.",
            "description": "To talk about distance, we can use ‘up to’ or ‘as far as’.",
            "answers": [
                "as far as",
                "up to",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c466ea3a51546e0af2ea13424472e5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is another three weeks ............................... the holidays.",
            "description": "We can use ‘to’ when counting the time until a future event. Until is also possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "until",
                "for",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "344b1b2317554e6192defddf7e5a1202"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know how she manages to support such a large family. She has nothing ................................... her pension.",
            "description": "After negative expressions like ‘no’, ‘nobody’ and ‘nothing’, all of these three expressions can have the same meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "besides",
                "except",
                "apart from",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2a15a4111aea4d45bf86eac4febafefd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you wearing anything ………………………. your sweater?",
            "description": "‘Underneath’ can be used as a preposition instead of ‘under’. But note that ‘underneath’ can only show position. ‘Under’, on the other hand, can also mean ‘lower than’.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "Either under or underneath"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "d685bc55925240a6b4bcfd32feb6a737"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind? I was ……………………………. you!",
            "description": "‘Before’ is possible here. ‘Before’ can be used to talk about the order in which people or things come in lists, queues, etc. ‘In front of’ is also correct here. It shows position.",
            "answers": [
                "in front of",
                "in front off",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "279451771f1d44fc9ab6638067b70178"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should arrive ……………………… their place ……………………. time …………………… lunch.",
            "description": "‘Arrive’ is followed by ‘at’ or ‘in’. ‘In time’ means ‘before the planned time’. The option ‘for’ is also correctly used.",
            "answers": [
                "at, in, for",
                "in, to, at",
                "at, for, in",
                "at, by, for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55be9ae636cd41b9a9fa0dcada1fd04f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They live ………………………. a small one bedroom flat ………………….. the third floor.",
            "description": "‘In’ shows position inside something. We use ‘on’ for the number of the floor.",
            "answers": [
                "in, in",
                "on, on",
                "in, on",
                "on, in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eeed8833bdda491dabe36939d4be571f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Granny is arriving ………………………. the 30 train.",
            "description": "We use ‘on’ and ‘off’ to talk about travel using public transport (buses, planes, trains, etc).",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "440a8d7898bb414da0a5cd03893cc0bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Last year, there were a large number of mangoes ……………………. the tree.",
            "description": "‘On’ can mean ‘attached to’. The mangoes are attached to the tree.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "63e59b558c414df9a04b670d39e51e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "His house is ……………………….. the way from Mumbai to Thane.",
            "description": "To indicate position on a line (for example a road or a river), we use ‘on’.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "63bc9771c0bc4e538082b8f4a4ff05b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He met and fell in love with a French girl when he was ………………………. the London School of Economics.",
            "description": "‘At’ is used to say where people study.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cb0e07be3d64d37b5cb7c5ad567b2cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "A few days after the accident she died ……………………….. the injuries.",
            "description": "We say ‘die of’ or ‘die from’.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from",
                "Either of or from"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b8fca8122c1a46e2822b2c077fd1b7c5"
        }
    ]
}